Finding Aid for the Alfred Leonard and Joseph Leonard Collection PASC-M.0180
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Catalogues and Brochures, Series XI.
  - [List of articles mentioning Ernst Toch]. mimeograph; 8 p. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Unknown source.
  - [List of Toch compositions with annotations]. mimeograph; 8 p. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    4 items: July 1939; August 1939; September, 1939; Music for Children special bulletin.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    3 items: October 1939; November 1939; December 1939.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    7 items: January 1940; February 1940; March 1940; April 1940; May 1940; June 1940; July 1940.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    5 items: August 1940; September 1940; October 1940; November 1940; Christmas edition.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    6 items: January 1941; February 1941; March 1941; April 1941; May 1941; June 1941.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    5 items: July 1941; August 1941; September 1941; October 1941; November 1941.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    7 items: January 1942; February 1942; March 1942; April 1942; May 1942; June 1942; blank information index card inserted in February 1942 bulletin.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    5 items: July 1942; August 1942; order form; October 1942; November 1942.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    7 items: February 1943; March 1943; April-May 1943; June-July 1943; August 1943; September 1943; volume 5 nos. 10-12.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    7 items: January-February 1943; March 1944; April-May 1944; July-August 1944; September 1944; October 1944; vol 6 nos. 11-12.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    6 items, all from 1945: vol. 7 no. 1; vo. 7 nos. 2-3; vol. 7 nos. 4-5 (2 copies); vol. 7 nos. 8-9; Christmas edition.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    5 items, all from 1946: vol. 8 nos. 1-3; vol. 8 nos. 4-5; August vol. 8 nos. 6-8; October vol. 8 nos. 9-10; November-December vol. 8 nos. 11-12.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    4 items: January-April 1947; May-June 1947; July-September 1947; October-December 1947.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    2 items: January-July 1948; August 1948.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    2 items: July 1949; Christmas 1949 issue.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    3 items: March 1951; November 1951; Christmas 1951 edition.
  - Gateway to Music Bulletin. catalogue. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    1 item: May 1952.
- Photographs, Series XII.
  - Photograph of Joseph Leonard at piano. 2x2 Kodak. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    Joseph Leonard at right at piano; unidentified man seated on left. Dated 1966. Original location in front of Alfred Leonard scrapbook, clipped to Joseph Leonard material. See 8/5.
  - Marianne and Klaus Arker. photo; 2x3.5. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Photo dated February 1937, Mannheim.
  - [Photo of a couple]. photo; 4.5x5.5. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    No information.
  - [Photo of conductor]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - [Envelopes for photographs]. 2 envelopes. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    2 items: envelope from Columbia Concerts; envelope from Ernst E. Gottlieb. Contents missing.
  - [Alfred Leonard at record player]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - [Alfred Leonard at radio dials]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - [Alfred Leonard with records at radio station]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - [Artur Schnabel with string quartet]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Photograph by Ernest Gottlieb.
  - [Artur Schnabel with string quartet]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - [Artur Schnabel with string quartet]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - [Artur Schnabel with 2 members of string quartet]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    Photographed by Ernest Gottlieb.
  - [Artur Schnabel with string quartet]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - [Close up of Artur Schnabel]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    Photograph by Otto Rothschild.
  - [Close up of Artur Schnabel]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - [Close up of Artur Schnabel]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - [Close up of Artur Schnabel]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - [Alfred Leonard posing by records and tapes at radio station]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - [PR photo of Joseph Leonard at keyboard]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - [Joseph Leonard]. photo; 5.75x7.5. (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - [Mario Castelnuevo Tedesco and Alfred Leonard]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 20)
    Photograph by Bernard M. Cohen.
  - [Ernst Toch; early photo]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - [Ernst Toch; late photo]. photo; 8x10. (Box 22, Folder 22)
    Photo by Esther Brown.
  - [Photo of unidentified seated man]. photo; 5.5x10. (Box 22, Folder 23)
    Photo taken by Ernest E. Gottleib.
- Sound Recordings, Series XIII.
  - 78 rpm Recordings - Published, Subseries 1.
    - Schubert, Franz. Karl Erb singt Lieder von Franz Schubert. Odeon WDLP 587. (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Contains Der Winterabend; Wer nie sein Brot mit Tranen ass; Das Zugenglocklein; Auf der Riesenkoppe; Nachstruck. Record and jacket.
    - Beethoven, Ludwig von. Rasoumovsky no. 2 Quartet no. 8 in E minor, op. 59, no. 2. RCA Victor LM 7001. (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Performed by the Paganini Quartet, with Henri Temianka, 1st violin; Gustave Roseels, 2nd violin; Robert Coute, viola; Robert Mass, cello. Record and jacket. Note on back of jacket: "For Marjorie, with the affection and friendship of Henri [Temianka] Xmas 1952".
    - Boyer, Lucienne. Visions in the Smoke/Speak to me of love. Columbia BD 673. (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Songs in French.
    - Gilbert and Sullivan. Scharfrichter-Couplet/Das Lied von der Bachstelze [From Mikado]. Electrola ?618. (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Performed by Max Pallenberg. Jacket missing.
    - [Piano by J. Leonard?]. record jacket. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - [78 rpm jacket with pencil drawings]. record jacket. (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Drawings of men's heads, "Love Song" and "Helen".
    - [Estrellita]. record jacket. (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Jacket labeled "Estrellita" "11-1".
  - 78 rpm Recordings - Unpublished, Subseries 2.
    - [Aida]. unlabeled 78 rpm record. (Box 9, Folder 8)
      One side has "Leonard Aida" scratched in.
    - [Unidentified 78 rpm recording]. unlabeled 78 rpm record. (Box 9, Folder 9)
      No identifying information.
    - Stravinsky, Igor. Pulcinella Suite. RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Recording of Otto Klemperer, N. Y.; 11-11-1935.
    - Brahms, Johannes; Verdi, Giuseppe. Brahms Symphony no. 1; Introduction to Aida. RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Side 1: Otto Klemperer with N. Y. Philharmonic 12/1/1935 performing Brahms Symphony no. 1; side 2 Introduction to Aida November 29, 1935.
    - [Unidentified 78 rpm recording]. RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - [Unidentified 78 rpm recording]. RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - [Unidentified 78 rpm recording]. RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - [Unidentified 78 rpm recording]. RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - [Unidentified 78 rpm recording]. RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - [Unidentified 78 rpm recording]. RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - [Unidentified 78 rpm recording]. RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Leonard, Joseph. Prelude and Fugue. Audiodisc 1062. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Rosenthal, Manuel. Dinner Music #1. Capitol Pro-Disc. (Box 9, Folder 20)
      10/13/46.
    - #1/#3. Capitol Pro-Disc. (Box 9, Folder 21)
      No other identifying information.
    - #2/#4. Capitol Pro-Disc. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - #5/#7. Capitol Pro-Disc. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - #6/#8. Capitol Pro-Disc. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - #10/#12. Capitol Pro-Disc. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - #11/#13. Capitol Pro-Disc. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - #14. Capitol Pro-Disc. (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Burroughs, Al. [Unidentified recording]. Audiodisc Recording Blank. (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Leonard, Joseph. Three Guesses/Album Leaf. Quality. (Box 9, Folder 29)
      Side 1: "Three Guesses to Joanne and Nora from Uncle Joseph August 1947"; side 2 Album Leaf by Joseph Leonard.
    - [Unidentified 78 rpm recording]. Radiotone Instantaneous Disc. (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - [Unidentified 78 rpm recording]. National Recording Disc. (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - [Unidentified 78 rpm recording]. The Music Shop - Hollywood. (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig von. Sonate Pathetique 2nd Movement. National Recording Disc. (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Beethoven and Schubert Improvisation and Interpretation. National Recording Disc. (Box 9, Folder 34)
      Title information found on accompanying record sleeve.
    - [Unidentified 78 rpm recording]. National Recording Disc. (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - 33 rpm Recordings - Unpublished, Subseries 3.
    - Anfang/Ende. 33 rpm RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 36)
      Labeled "Anfang 14 Nov. 1945/Ende".
    - Handel, Georg. Water Music Overture. 33 rpm RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 37)
      Labeled "Handel: Watermusic Overture Klemperer + NY Philharmonic 12/1/35".
    - [Record jacket]. Jacket to 33 rpm RCA Victor Blank for Home Recording. (Box 9, Folder 38)
      In pencil "Zverst spielen"; records 36 and 37 found inside this jacket.
    - [Unidentified 33 rpm recording]. 33 rpm RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - [Unidentified 33 rpm recording]. 33 rpm RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - [Unidentified 33 rpm recording]. 33 rpm RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - [Unidentified 33 rpm recording]. 33 rpm RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - [Unidentified 33 rpm recording]. 33 rpm RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - [Unidentified 33 rpm recording]. 33 rpm RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - [Unidentified 33 rpm recording]. 33 rpm RCA Victor Home Recording Record. (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - 33 rpm Recordings - Published, Subseries 4.
    - Beethoven, Ludwig van. 32 Sonatas from Beethoven Society Edition by Artur Schnabel. RCA Victor Red Seal Collectors LM 9500; 13 33 rpm record set. (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Perfomed by Artur Schnabel. 13 33 rpm set part of Limited Beethoven Society Edition contains boxed set with volume 1 of 32 sonatas (sheet music); liner notes on recordings; 13 rpm records of performances by Artur Schnabel. See remainder of box of box 8 for liner notes; volume 1 and volume 2 of sheet music. Original box discarded due to mold.
    - McKenna, Siobhan. [Interview]. RCA Victor G8OH-9062. (Box 9, Folder 46)
      Interviewed by George R. Marek.
  - Reel to Reel Tapes, Subseries 6.
    - KFAC Program 3/2 No. 1. 7 in. reel. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Toch, Ernst. Prinzessin auf der Erbse. 7 in. reel; single track; 7 1/2 ips. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - [Leonard, Joseph]. #1-8 of Composer's Workshop/#9 Un'sene tokef. 7 in. reel; 7 1/2 ips. (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Track 1: #1-8 of Composer's Workshop I I/12/60; Track 2: #9 Un'sene tokef [composition by Joseph Leonard] 1/12/60.
    - Toch, Ernst. Motley Suite Opus 48 (1927). 7 in. reel; single track; 7 1/2 ips. (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Suite contains: Marschtempo; Intermezzo; Adagio Espressivo; Mationetten - Tanz; Galante Passacalglia; Karussel. Performed by N.A.A.C.C. Symphony Orchestra, conducted by H. Arthur Brown. Recorded in performance Sunday, April 28, 1963 at Royce Hall, UCLA.
    - Wellez, Egon. Quartet No. 6. 7 in. reel. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - [B.S.O. Lunschof Cond.]. 7 in. reel; 7 1/2 ips. (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Possibly Boston Symphony Orchestra with Lunschof conducting.
    - Ginastera. Quartet No. 1. 7 in. reel; 7 1/2 ips. (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Performed by Paganini Quartet, recorded by Decca records. Master tape used on KFAC January 1, 1956.
    - [Unidentified orchestral music]. 7 in. reel; 7 1/2 ips. (Box 10, Folder 8)
      On box: "Boston Symphony Erich Leinsdorf Cond[ucting] Side 1".
    - Tchaikovsky, Peter. [Unidentified piano music]. 7 in. reel; 7 1/2 ips.; stereo. (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Performances by Yi-Kwei-Sze, Victor Babin, dated 12/1/71.
    - Leonard, Joseph. Romanza. 7 in. reel; 7 1/2 ips. (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Note on box: "Side I 'Romanza' Joseph Leonard. There are 3 copies on this tape. It is recorded at 7 1/2 ips."
    - Toch, Ernst. Big Ben. 7 in. reel; 7 1/2 ips. (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Perfomed by Pittsburg Symphony, conducted by William Steinberg.
    - Rachmaninoff, Sergei. [Unidentified piece]. 7 in. reel; 7 1/2 ips.; stereo. (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Performaners listed as Yi-Kwei Sze; Victor Babin, dated 12/1/71.
    - [Friday eve. 4/22 for Joseph]. 7 in. reel. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig von. Second Rasumovsky Quartet. 7 in. reel. (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Wednesday, November 16, 1955.
    - Schubert, Franz. Eb Trio 3rd and 4th Movements; Schubert Bb Trio 1st Movement. 7 in. reel. (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Contents listed on back as: Schubert Eb Trio 3rd and 4th Movements; Schubert Bb Trio 1st Movement. Performance by Szigeti, Van der Burg and Jaidenberg(?); 5/25/47.
    - Brahms, Johannes; Schubert, Franz. Brahms Trio 4th movement; Schubert Trio in Eb 1st and 2nd movements. 7 in. reel. (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Performed by Szigeti, Van der Burg and Jaidenberg(?); 5/24/47.
    - Bach; Mendelssohn; Schubert; Debussy. [Keyboard pieces]. 7 in. reel; 7 1/2 ips.; stereo. (Box 11, Folder 8)
      4 items performed by Joseph Leonard: Bach Prelude and Fugue in D Minor; Mendelssohn Song without words; Schubert Allegretto C minor, Allegro assai, Valses nobles opus 77; Debussy Le petit negre. Dated May 29, 1977.
    - Mozart; Bach. Sonata in C; Prelude and Fugue no. 8. 7 in. reel; 7 1/2 ips. (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Performance by Joseph Leonard April 1969.
    - Leonard, Joseph. Friday Service 8/10/73. 7 in. reel. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Toch, Ernst. Peter Pan. 7 in. reel; 7 1/2 ips.; stereo. (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Contents listed on box as: Thru parts; Allegro grazioso; Andante semplice e grazioso; Allegro vivo. performed by the Indianopolis Symphony Orchestra, conducted by Izler Solomon. Recorded February 10, 1957 at the Mimat Theatre.
    - Tchaikovsky; Arensky; Rimsky-Korsakoff; Benjamin; Stravinsky; Copeland; Strauss. 176 Keys Music for Two Pianos. RCA Victor FTC-2034 Red Seal; 7 in. reel; 4 track stereo; 7 1/2 ips. (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Commercial recording, performed by Vitya Vronsky and Victor Babin, duo pianists.
    - [Ceremony honoring Joseph Leonard - Part 1]. 7 in. reel; 3 3/4 ips. (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Note on back "Honoring Joseph Leonard Dec 9-[19]63."
    - [Ceremony honoring Joseph Leonard - Part 2]. 7 in. reel. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Bach; Beethoven; Strauss; Ibert. [Performance by Joseph Leonard sent as birthday present]. 7 in. reel. (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Cover lists: Bach 18 Little Preludes 1st series; Bach 2nd series 6 Little Preludes, Complete; Bach Prelude and Fugue in Bb minor; Beethoven Sonata, opus 14 nr. 2; Richard Strauss Trumerei; Ibert Le Petit Ane Blanc. Box also has note: "April 1974, Happy Birthday to you both! Love Joseph." Tape missing from box.
    - [Kapell Selections Reel 2]. 7 in. reel. (Box 12, Folder 7)
      No other information given.
    - Bach, Johann Sebastian. Partita #4 in D - Kapell 3. 7 in. reel. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Schubert, Franz; Liszt, Franz. Landler; Impromptu in Ab; Mephisto Waltz; Hungarian Rhapsody no. 11 Kapell 4. 7 in. reel. (Box 12, Folder 9)
      No other information.
    - [Salomone de Rossi Ebreo]. Concert - A Sixteenth Century Service Celebrating Jewish Music Month. 7 in. reel. (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Box labeled as "Schubert Unfinished and Symphony no. 5 Reiner/Chicago Symphony'; concert program to A sixteenth Century Service Celebrating Jewish Music Month located inside box (see 20/10 for program); presumably original commercial tape was recorded over. Concert held at Temple Beth Am as part of Friday Sabbath service March 5, 1963, featuring music composed by Salomone de Rossi Ebreo.
    - Toch, Ernst. Symphony #2 Opus 73. 7 in. reel. (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Performance conducted by Antol Dorati. Note on box "La Forge copy"; "Hancock tape".
    - Echoes of High Fidelity Side 1. UHF-1A; 7 in. reel; 15 ips. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Whitaker, Thomas R. Commencement address "He is Us". 7 in. reel; single track; 3 3/4 ips. (Box 13, Folder 4)
      002-015 introduction by E. Pannis; 016-253 T. Whitaker.
    - Babin, Victor. Concerto de Camera #3. 7 in. reel; 7 1/2 ips; stereo. (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Mixed ensembles. Recorded 4/12/72.
    - Toch, Ernst. Bass Quartet; Quartet op. 74; Music for Woodwinds and Percussion. 7 in. reel; 7 1/2 ips. (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Bass Quartet performed by Eudice Shapiro Quartet; Quartet op. 74 performed by Roth Quartet; recorded January 8 and 10, 1960. Artists for Music for Woodwinds and Percussions recorded 10/12/59 at Monday Evening Concert; artists not specified.
    - Yours is my Heart Alone. 7 in. reel; 4 track 7 1/2 ips. (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Information on box: RCA file FTC-2140 4/1/63; source N2RY 2864; N2RY 2865; PRRS 3350; 3351. Appears to master of recording performed by Robert Shaw Chorale.
    - Toch, Ernst. Peter Pan. 7 in. reel. (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Performed by Louisville Orchestra.
    - Offman, Jean; Sanderson, Alex; Leonard, Alfred. 7 in. reel. (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Names Jean Offman, Alex Sanderson, Alfred Leonard on side of box. No other information.
    - Brahms, Johannes. Trio. 7 in. reel. (Box 13, Folder 10)
      Performers Josef Szigeti, Willem Van der Burg, Theo. Saidenberg. Movements 1-3.
    - Brahms, Johannes. Quartet in G minor; Quartet in C minor. 7 in. reel. (Box 13, Folder 11)
      Performers listed as L. Kaufrulau, Paul Robyn, Willem Van der Burg, Theo. Saidenberg.
    - [5-B 4/24/66 A track]. 7 in. reel. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - [No information on box]. 7 in. reel. (Box 13, Folder 13)
      Red Seal Magnetic Recording Sound Tape brand.
    - [No information on box]. 7 in. reel. (Box 13, Folder 14)
      Plain white box.
    - [No information on box]. 7 in. reel. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - [No information on box]. 7 in. reel. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - [No information on box]. 7 in. reel. (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - R/S and Victroll Sampler Jan. '68. 7 in. reel. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Hindemith. Quartet for Clarinet, Violin, Cello and Piano - Finale. 7 in. reel. (Box 14, Folder 2)
      "Reel #3". No other information.
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario. Tre Corali Ebraici. 5 in. reel; 7 1/2 ips. (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Note on back: 'Composer at the piano"; "In salute a Joseph da Clara C. T."
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario. Tre Corali Ebraici. 5 in. reel. (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Note on back: "Performance at Westside Jewish Community Center, January 29, 1958. Choral #1 & 2, Side 1; Choral #3, Side 2."
    - [Consecration and Bas Mitzvah ceremony]. 5 in. reel; 3 3/4 ips. (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Information on back regarding Susan Luggar's bas mitzvah ceremony has been crossed out in red; note on top in red "Consecration".
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario. The Fiery Furnace. 5 in. reel. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Toch, Ernst. Dedication. 5 in. reel. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Schubert, Franz. Die Schone Mullerin. 5 in. reel, 2-track mono. (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Performed by Peter Roberts, tenor; Joseph Leonard, piano in winter 1969. Side 1 contains numbers 1-10; side 2 contains 11-20.
    - [No information available]. 5 in. reel. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus; Schubert, Franz; Varess. Adagio and Fugue K. 546; Quartet in A minor Op. 29; Quartet no. 2. 10 1/2 in. reel. (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Recording dated Nov. 16, 1955 by Vegh Quartet includes; Mozart Adagio and Fugue K. 546; Schubert Quartet in AS minor, Op. 29 "Rosamunde"; Varess Quartet no. 2 - First performance.
    - Vivaldi; Mozart; Ibert; Rameau; Rossini, Hindemith. [Performance by The Woodwind Ensemble of Paris]. 10 1/2 in. reel. (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Recording of Music Guild sponsored performance; 4th concert of 11th season January 25, 1956, by The Woodwind Ensemble of Paris. Members: Jacques Castagnier, flute; Robert Casier, oboe; Andre Boutard, clarinet; Gerard Faisandier, bassoon; Michel Berges, horn. Pieces performed include: Concerto in G minor for flute, oboe and bassoon by Vivaldi; Divertimento no. 14 K. 270 for woodwind quartet by Mozart; Cassation in Eb for oboe, clarinet, horn and bassoon by Mozart; Trois Pieces Breves for wind quartet by Ibert; Symphonies and dances for woodwind quintet by Rameau; Quatuor no. 2 by Rossini; Kleine Kammermusik opus 24, no. 2 by Hindemith.
    - [No information available]. 10 1/2 in. reel. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - CDs, Subseries 7.
    - Leonard, P. Alfred; Leonard, Joseph. Recordings from the [19]30s and 40s Volume 1. CD. (Box 14, Folder 10)
      Material transfered from reel to reel tapes and 78s. Volume 1 contains: Letter from Mannheim; Thank you Joseph Feb. 24, 1941; Hollywood Anti-Nazi league presents Joseph Leonard; Radio news and conversation; Comments on La Traviata, April 17, 1937; P. A. Leonard interviews Dimitri Tiomkin Jan. 25, 1937; Concert introduction Nov. 12, 1935; Fledermaus introduction Nov. 10, 1935.
    - Leonard, P. Alfred; Leonard, Joseph. Recordings from the [19]30s and 40s Volume 2. CD. (Box 14, Folder 11)
      Material transfered from reel to reel tapes and 78s. Volume 2 contains: Five short pieces by Joseph Leonard (Hollywood Anti Nazi League broadcast); Piano composition by Joseph Leonard; Joseph Leonard, piano; Prelude and Fugue for Piano by Joseph Leonard; Fantasy for Organ (by JL?); Robert Maas plays Bach cello suites; I-IV Satz (string quartet by JL?); Songs (Bach, Strauss); Toscanini orchestra rehearsal.